pharmacy-xl.com 2019-11-09

# Privacy Policy of Pharmacy XL

### Privacy Policy

Our website address is: https://www.pharmacy-xl.com which is fully secure SSL website. This is the privacy policy of Pharmacy XL ( https://www.pharmacy-xl.com ) and valid while browsing our website, when making an order or submitting a question via the contact form etc.

### What personal data we collect and why we collect it?

When customers leave questions or comments on the site we collect the data shown in the contact form, and also the visitors IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you make an order and/or have an account with us and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

### Who we share your data with and How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that order and register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time or request deletion of data and unsubscribe from our newsletters. Our website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### What rights you have over your data?

If you have an account on this site, or after ordering, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you by simply filling out the contact form. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

##### Where we send your data?

Visitor comments, order form or ordinary messages may be checked through an automated spam detection service for your safety and security.

###### Terms and Conditions

Please also check out our Terms and Conditions set out in full here.

#### Privacy Statement - Your privacy is important to us

Your information is yours only. We protect the privacy of our customers by enforcing strict no-third-parties policy. Rest assured that your personal details, payment and medical information go nowhere beyond the order submission phase. We recommend reading our Privacy Policy in full if you are interested. We have an ever growing number of returning customer thanks to our low prices, good quality medicines and because customers are happy how we treat their privacy.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Any order information, including credit card numbers and contact information (such as email address), will be used only to fill your orders. You are welcome to read our Privacy Statement in full and we are using the latest SSL technologies for encrypting your data.

##### Shipping and Handling

All orders are shipped via Registered Airmail and require recipients' signature upon delivery. Please note that orders placed on Fridays after 4PM will be processed the following Monday.

Delivery time is subject to shipping addresses as well as national and religious holidays, and may vary from one order to another.

You can track your order by going to our Order Status page and entering your email address and a password, which you will receive to your email once your order has been accepted.

### Site Security

Our site takes extreme care to protect customers against the loss or misuse of information under our control. All medical and financial transactions occur over encrypted communication channels utilizing a 256-bit SSL certificate.

Please feel free to contact us with any questions or concerns you may have.

Enjoy browsing our Online Pharmacy and enjoy your quality medicines from Pharmacy XL - the biggest online pharmacy for drugs without prescription and free shipping worldwide.

  * __**Trusted Meds**

All 100% genuine

  * __**Hassle-Free Refunds**

Easy 30-day money back

  * __**Shop with Assurance**

SSL security technology

  * __**Free Shipping**

Fast and far-reaching
